声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：Requiem校对扣扣
后期：阿胜 双语制作：e0yue
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
我在海滩上发现了电缆
I found the wire on the beach.
我想可能与我们
I thought it might have something to do
接收到的信号有关
with a transmission we picked up,
一个法国女人不停的发射了16年
a Frenchwoman repeating on a loop for 16 years.
真的有那么久吗?
Has it really been that long?
你在这个岛上还见过其他人吗?
Have you seen other people on this island?
但是我听见了他们说话
But I hear them.
他们窃窃私语
They whisper.
我们得离开这个岛
We need to get off this island.
你在暗示什么吗?
Are you suggesting something?
是的
Yeah.
我们造了一个筏子
We build a raft.
进展的不错啊
You're making a lot of progress.
是的  努力在做
Yeah, trying.
我把竹子铺在上面
Got this bamboo for the decking,
留一些空间来做船舱
a piece of the fuselage for the cabin.
会弄好的
It'll work.
我们能搞定
We can do this.
最近每天下午都在下雨
It's been raining every afternoon.
那意味着季风季节已经到了
That means that we are on the cusp of monsoon season.
我们为什么要听Arzt的?
Why are we listening to Arzt?
你只不过是个高中老师
You're a damn high school science teacher.
我只是在想你们不会想死吧?
I was just assuming you didn't want to die.
那么我们该什么时候走?
So when do we have to leave?
昨天
Yesterday.
你在干什么?
What're you doing?
看电视
Watching TV.
你知道现在是什么时间吗? 赶快去睡觉  Walt
Oh, man, you see what time it is? Go back to sleep, Walt.
我一直都在看这个节目
I always watch this show.
好吧  那么...
Okay, then.
你能不能把声音调低点?
Could you at least turn it down?
我说的是把声音调低  Walt
I said turn it down, Walt.
我过去看这个节目时 Brian从来不管我调多大声音
Brian lets me watch it as loud as...
我不是Brian
I'm not Brian.
气死我了
Dang.
-我们走 Vincent  -嘿  你要去哪里?
-Let's go, Vincent.  -Hey, where are you going? Hey!
Walt!
离我远点! 不要管我!
Get away from me. Leave me alone.
-不要想... 不要从我身边离开!  -我说了 离我远点
-Don't even... Don't you think...  -I said get away from me.
Walt 听着 我不这样认为
I don't think so. Come on.
放开我!
Get off of me!
听着  我也不喜欢这样
I don't like this, either.
但是你必须上飞机
But you're getting on that plane.
不  我才不想去呢
-发生了什么  -没什么  我是他父亲
-What's going on?  -It's okay. I'm his father.
不  你不是我父亲
You're not my father!
你不是我父亲
-爸爸! 爸爸  醒醒  -什么事?
-Dad, wake up!  -What?
-什么事?  -有人来了!
-What?  -Somebody's here.
停下来!
Hey! Hey! Stop!
慢...慢点儿
Slow, slow down.
那是谁?
Who is that?
那肯定是那个法国女人
Gotta be the French chick.
大家冷静
Calm down, everyone.
没什么
It's all right.
Danielle?
你来这儿干什么?
What are you doing here?
"The others"要来了
The others are coming.
迷 失
第一季 第二十三集
压制：寂高心
YYeTs美剧翻译组制作
www.YYETS.net
我们的船16年到达这个岛
Our ship went aground on this island 16 years ago.
当时我们有六个人
There were six of us.
我们小组  六个人
My team. Six.
那时候
By that time,
我已经怀孕七个月了
I was already seven months pregnant.
孩子在我手里抱着
I delivered the infant myself.
当时孩子和我在一起只有一个星期
The baby and I were together for only one week,
然后我看见了黑烟
when I saw black smoke.
5公里远处冒出缕缕黑烟
A pillar of black smoke five kilometers inland.
那天晚上...
That night...
他们来了
they came.
他们来了...
they came...
带走了她
and took her.
Alex
他们抢走了我的孩子
They took my baby.
而现在...
And now...
他们又来了
they're coming again.
冲着你们所有的人
They're coming for all of you.
谁要来?
Who's coming?
The others
你们只有三个选择
You have only three choices.
逃跑...
Run...
藏起来...
Hide...
或者死
Or die.
这个女人炸掉了自己的藏身之处
This is a woman who blew up her own shelter.
而现在她又在谈论什么看见黑烟和听见低声细语
Now she talks about black smoke and hearing whispers.
我的意思是说 她是不是疯了
She's not playing with a full deck.
那并不意味着她说的就不是真的
That doesn't mean what she's saying isn't true.
那么 假如你相信她说的  随便你
If you wanna focus on the "what ifs", be my guest.
但是我要去做些实际的东西
I'm sticking with the tangible,
现在要做的就是
and right now that's
让筏子下水
the launching of the raft.
弄得怎么样了?
How's it going?
我想今天离开
I wanted to get off today,
但是  实际上
but realistically,man,
把舵弄好后
after we get the rudder done,
我们仍然需要铺滚木把它弄下水
we still gotta lay the rails to get her down to the water.
但是在你弄舵的同时 我们铺设滚木不是更快?
Wouldn't it save time to lay the rails while you are finishing the rudder?
人手不够
Manpower shortage.
你需要什么来铺设滚木和移动船?
What do you need to lay the rails and move the boat?
今天全部完成?
Get it all done today?
所有的人倒差不多
Pretty much everybody.
好吧  给我20分钟
All right, give me 20 minutes.
找到尽可能多的圆木
Grab as many palm tree logs as you can find,
越长越好
the longer the better,
把它们拿到筏子那里   Michael知道怎么使用它们
take them over to the raft area.Michael knows what to do with them.
好的 一会见
See ya then.
你要把它们绑紧
You need to get 'em in there tight,
用杠杆把它弄上轨道
and you need leverage to get 'em on the rails.
知道了  好的
Yeah, that's good.
好  干的不错
Good. That's good.
好  干的不错兄弟
Okay, that's good, man.
一定要稳住  好吗?
Just get it under there, okay?
好的
Okay.
-你还好吧?  -是的
-You all right?  -Yep.
大家听着我数数
So listen, on my count,
我会喊 "1 2 3"
I'll do, "one, two, three, lift,"
抬起来然后推 明白了么?
and then push, okay?
知道了?
Got it?
好吧  来吧
Okay, come on.
一旦我们把它弄到了吃水线
Once it's down to the water line,
我们就放下来 然后装上东西
we'll drop it and load it up.
好了
All right.
准备好
Ready?
开始了
1!
One.
2!
Two.
起!
Lift!
推!
Push!
加油  同志们!
Come on, guys.
推!
Push. Push!
用杠杆!
Use your levers.
好了  干的好  干的好
Yeah. Good, good.
1  2  3! 抬起来!
One, two, three, lift.
保持好方向!
Hey, keep it straight.
噢  不!
Oh, no! Come on!
真不敢相信!
I can't believe this.
真难以置信
Can't believe it.
你看我干什么 又不是我的错
What are you looking at me for?
你没控制好杠杆
You missed the lever!
就是因为你才不能控制好方向
You couldn't keep the raft straight!
我不能控制好方向
I couldn't keep it straight?
爸爸!  看!
Dad! Look.
他们有多少人?
How many of them are there?
我把知道的都告诉你们了
I told you all I know.
肯定还有什么你没有告诉我们 你是怎么知道的?
There has to be more to tell. How did you know?
你们最大的麻烦就是
You have a bigger problem.
我可以藏到树丛里
I can vanish into the jungle,
我只有一个人
but I'm just one person.
你们有40个人
You have 40 people.
他们可以藏在哪里?
Where will you hide them?
伙计  哇哦
Dude. Whoa.
这是什么?
What is this?
我们希望你能告诉我们
We hoped you could tell us.
从来没见过这种东西
I've never seen anything like it.
呃  有个问题
Uh, question.
怎么把所有的人都藏到里面去?
How do you know we can all, like, fit in there?
外面没有把手
No handle outside,
意味着肯定有其他方法可以进去
must be another way in.
-另外一个地方意味着空地  -这是一个错误
-Another entrance means space.  -This is a mistake.
我们对"The others"一无所知
We don't know about these others.
我们在没有信息
We're reacting with no information,
没有智慧的情况下反抗
no intelligence.
这个仓口也许就是他们的
This might even be theirs.
地平线上的黑烟并不意味着...
Black smoke that are rising doesn't mean...
那意味着他们要来了
It means they're coming.
没错 我们都知道
Yeah, we got that.
你藏身地方的陷阱有炸药
You booby-trapped your shelter with explosives.
剩下的还有吗?
You have any more?
在黑岩那里
At the Black Rock.
黑暗地带
In the Dark Territory.
这下可好 有三个理由能去那里了
That's three reasons to go right there.
要想在日落前回来
If we're to make it back by sunset,
必须在一小时之内出发
we have to leave within the hour.
加柠檬的龙色兰酒
Tequila and tonic with a wedge of lemon.
你们为什么事吵架?
Why were you yelling?
服务台的那个女孩
The girl at the check-in counter.
你冲她又喊又叫的
You were yelling at her.
不好意思 恩...
I'm sorry, uh...
咱们认识么?
do I know you?
我和你一趟航班  去洛山机
I'm on your flight. LA.
你父亲死了  是么?
So, your dad died, huh?
我想你肯定不知道我为什么又喊又叫
I thought you didn't hear what I was yelling about.
我并不想冒犯
I was being polite.
我父亲去世了
my dad died.
因为什么?
How?
心脏病发作
A heart attack.
不是因为喝酒  是吧?
Not a drinker, huh?
不  不  不全是
No, not really.
没有戒指是因为你单身还是因为你不喜欢戴?
No ring 'cause you're single or because you don't like wearing one?
你是问我结婚没有?
You asking me if I'm married?
你结婚了吗?
Are you married?
没有  没有  不再是了
No, not anymore.
要再来一杯加柠檬的龙色兰酒吗?
Can we get another tequila and tonic, please?
我想你没有听我说话
I didn't think you were listening.
那么你叫什么名字?
So, what's your name?
Ana-Lucia
那告诉我  Ana-Lucia
So, tell me, Ana-Lucia,
你为什么在早上10点喝加柠檬的龙色兰酒?
why are you drinking tequila and tonics at ten to noon?
我讨厌坐飞机
I hate flying.
而他们让我坐在飞机的后部
And they stuck me all the way in the back of the plane
起落架就在我脚下
where the wheels come down right under your damn feet.
那么你坐哪儿?
So, where are you sitting?
23B
42F
想要换着坐吗?
Wanna trade?
是的  我在Sydney
Hey. Yeah, I'm in Sydney.
稍等
Hold on.
不好意思
Sorry...
Uh, Jack.
Jack  我要回电话
Jack. I gotta talk.
到飞机上再喝  好吗?
Um... we'll have the next drink on the plane, okay?
42F  没错
42 F. Right.
还有  Jack...
And, Jack?
不好的事情都已经过去了
The worst part's over.
听着  我知道每个人都很害怕
Look, I know you're all scared.
而且我也知道每个人都有很多问题要问
And I know that everybody has a lot of questions.
我现在能告诉大家的就是我们有一个计划
All I can tell you right now is that we do have a plan.
我们要到丛林里拿些补给
We've got to go into the jungle for supplies.
几个小时后回来
We'll be back in a few hours.
同时  尽一切可能帮Michael把筏子弄下水
In the meantime, do everything you can to help Michael get that raft on the water.
完成后  到山洞那里去
And after that, go to the caves.
我们会尽快回来  我保证
We'll be back as soon as we can. I promise.
说的好
Hey, nice speech.
计划虽然有点缺陷  但是  没有什么是完美的
Plan's a little flawed, but nobody's perfect.
是的  你的计划  你要到丛林里去
Your plan. Go in the jungle,
拿些炸药  炸开仓口
and get dynamite and blow open a hatch,
然后你要把大家藏在里面
and then hide everyone inside.
你想保持秘密  就不要告诉那个胖子
You wanna keep a secret,don't tell the fat guy.
你想要干什么Arzt?
What do you want, Arzt?
天知道炸药离这里有多远
God knows how long that dynamite might has been out there.
但是从我的判断  那个疯狂的夫人并不关心这个
And from what I can tell,Madame Nutsodoesn't seem too concerned with how to handle it.
所以除非你想放弃计划
So unless you want to blow up
带上我一起去
I'm coming with you.
没问题
Okay.
找些水  我们半小时后出发
Grab some water bottles.We're leaving in a half an hour.
绳索还可以用  但是我们需要新的桅杆
We can salvage the cables, but we need new bamboo for the mast.
我们需要在开始前弄好方向舵
We need to fix the rudder before we even start to think about that.
-需要帮忙吗?  -首先把这个做好
-You need help?  Let's get this done first.
这不是我的错
Hey, this wasn't my fault.
让我一起帮忙吧
So put me to work.
不想冒犯 只是这样我们能更快些  好吗?
No offense.We just work faster this way, okay?
没错 就是这样   你认为我在这里干什么?
All right! What do you think I'm doing over here?
还认识我么?
You remember me?
三天前
Three nights ago.
你因为打架被带到这里
You were hauled in here thrashing and fighting.
来得时候  还踢坏了我的桌子
As you were being escorted by,you kicked my desk.
打坏了我杯子
And you broke my mug.
漂亮的小孩
Nice kids.
对你来说是悲哀的
Sadly for you,
打坏我的杯子不是你那天晚上犯的最大的错误
breaking my mug was not the most significant mistake you made that evening.
算了吧  博士  我不过是参与了一次酒吧打架
Come on, doctor.I got into a bar fight.
在这个国家那不是一种荣誉吗?
Ain't that a badge of honor in this country?
你知道在那个酒吧里被你用头撞的人是谁么?
You know who you head-butted in that bar?
你撞的是可敬的Warren Truss
You head-butted the Honorable Warren Truss...
农业  渔业和林业部长
...Minister of Agriculture,Fisheries and Forestry.
-最重要的一个  -是他用头撞我
-One of the most important...  -He head-butted me.
我们有证人证明他没有做
We have witnesses.He did no such thing.
当然
Course.
你认为这很好笑  James?
You think this is funny, James?
James Ford
伤害  电报诈骗  偷窃  银行诈骗  电话诈骗
Assault, wire fraud,identity theft, bank fraud,telemarketing fraud...
你是个垃圾
You're a blight, a stain, scavenger.
你是一个骗子  欺骗那些弱者和穷人
You're a con man preying11 on the weak and needy.
告诉我James 你怎样生活下来的?
Tell me something, James,how do you live with yourself?
我没干坏事
I do just fine.
真的么?
Do you?
你甚至不值得我们把你关进监狱
You're not even worth the cost to incarcerate you.
你被驱逐了
Which is why you're being deported.
今天下午坐飞机离开
Your plane leaves this afternoon.
还有  James
And, James,
你不准再踏进澳大利亚一步
you're banned from ever setting foot in Australia again.
你不必担心
Don't you worry.
-我再也不会回来了  -最好别回来  兄弟
-I ain't ever coming back here.  -Best not, mate.
伐木工人
A lumberjack.
什么?
Scuse me?
从来没有问过你你是干什么的  所以...
I never asked what you did back in the real world.
随便猜的
So I'm taking a wild guess.
伐木工人
Lumberjack.
有什么需要我帮忙的吗  医生? 因为我有事要做
Something I can help you with, doc?Cause I got work to do.
给你带来个东西
I got something for you.
你是要上筏子的人中唯一知道怎么用枪的人
You're the only one on the raft who knows how to use one.
我要枪干什么?
What do I need a gun for?
只是以放万一
Just in case.
你认为我们会用尽食物和水?
You think we're gonna run outta food and water?
我是不是应该让孩子远离痛苦?
I put the kid out of his misery?
只是以放万一
Just in case.
剩下的你打算怎么处理?
What're you doing with the rest of them?
交给Sayid了
Giving 'em to Sayid.
消失在丛林中 对吧?
Going into the jungle after the boomsticks, huh?
是啊
Yeah.
你们回来时  我们已经乘船走了
Time you get back,we'll be in the water.
这很可能就是再见了
Guess this is pretty much goodbye then.
是的  我想是了
Yeah, I guess it is.
祝你好运  Sawyer
Good luck, Sawyer.
大约在上飞机的前一周
About a week before we all got on the plane,
在悉尼的一个酒吧里和一个人聊天
I got to talking to this man in a bar in Sydney.
他也是美国人
He was an American too.
一个医生
A doctor.
我经历了些狂欢时光  但是这个人
I've been on some benders in my time,
他在争取时间记录
but this guy was going for an all-time record.
他有个儿子
So it turns out this guy has a son.
儿子也是个医生
Son's a doctor too.
他们曾经大吵了一场
They'd had some kinda big-time falling out.
这个人知道那是他的错
The guy knew it was his fault...
显然他的儿子也是这么认为的
even though his son was back in the States thinking the same damn thing.
你知道  孩子就像狗
See, kids are like dogs.
假如你对他们太严厉了
You knock 'em around enough,
他们会认为他们做错了什么
they'll think they did something to deserve it.
无论如何...
Anyway...
酒吧里有个付费电话
there's a pay phone in this bar,
这个人...
and this guy...
基督徒
Christian...
告诉我他有硬币想给他儿子打电话
tells me he wishes he had the stonesto pick up the phone and call his kid.
对他说"对不起"
Tell him he's sorry.
他是一个比他还出色的医生
That he's a better doctor than he'll ever be.
他非常骄傲
He's proud.
我必须中断  但是...
I had to take off...
感觉告诉我他后来一直没有打那个电话
but something tells me he never made that call.
世界真小   不是么?
Small world, huh?
是啊
Yeah.
保重  Jack
Good luck, Jack.
-你要全副武装?  -是的  先生  手枪
-You're gonna be armed?  -Yes, sir, an ankle holster.
你必须把这些东西放在行李仓前面的间隔间里
Stow this in the crew luggage compartment in front.
没有问题
No problemo.
你为什么要带五支枪?
Why do you need five guns?
你想告诉他吗 Kate?
Gee, you wanna tell him, Kate?
为什么我要带五支枪?
Why do I need five guns?
她不好意思了
She's shy.
那么这是什么?
What's this, then?
那是一个有趣的故事
That's a good story.
你想要说吗  kate?
You wanna tell it?Huh, Kate?
这东西是属于她的青梅竹马的
This belonged to her childhood sweetheart,
几年前在逃跑中被杀了
who she got killed a couple of years ago when she was on the run.
可怜的家伙   有一个妻子和一个两岁大的孩子
Poor guy. Had a wife.Two-year-old kid.
他叫什么来着?
What was his name?
这几年 在我追捕她的过程中  某个地方
Somewhere along the way during the three years I was chasing her,
她开始给我家里打电话询问怎样才能减轻罪行
she starts calling me at my house,and whining on about her mitigating circumstances.
但是她真正想做的...
But what she's really doing...
是奚落我
is taunting me.
所以我告诉她情人的玩具飞机
So I tell her that I've got what's-his-name's little toy airplane
在新墨西哥城的一个保险箱里
in a safe deposit box in New Mexico.
当她弄明白是哪个银行 哪个保险箱时
So she somehow figures out which bank,which safe deposit box.
骗一些白痴抢劫了那个银行
She seduces some idiot to rob the damn bank,
然后在利用完那个白痴后将其杀害
then puts a bullet in her new friend because she's done using him.
但是她分文不要
But she leaves all the money.
只拿走了这个飞机
She just takes the plane.
因为那是在她生命里唯一在乎的东西
Because that's the one thing in the whole world that Kate does care about.
她没有感情...
She has no attachments...
我想她告诉她自己
And I think she's telling herself
她需要这个来补偿他的男友...
She needs it to atone for killing her boyfriend,
他叫什么名字?
what's-his-name.
Kate  别这样  他叫什么来着?
Come on.What was his name?
Tom  你个贱人  啊!
Tom!It was Tom, you son of a bitch!
那就是我为什么需要五支枪
And that is why I need five guns.
你要去?
You're heading out?
是的
Yeah.
我在想也许我应该和你一起去
I was thinking that I might go with you...
因为以前那些事
for old time's sake.
我想要帮忙
I wanna help.
你不想在这里帮忙让筏子下水
You won't be here for the raft launching.
是的
Yeah,
我不擅长说再见
Well, I'm not very good at goodbyes.
收拾好你的东西
Grab your stuff.
谢谢  兄弟
Thanks, man.
好好保存
Keep it safe.
Locke  要带什么话吗?
Locke, you have a message?
我们要上筏子了
It's going on the raft.
你知道   "亲爱的妈妈   我一切都好  现在在岛上...
You know, "Dear Mom,everything's fine. I'm on the island.
除非  当然  放黑烟的人出现   亲爱的"  署名
Unless the Black Smoke People turn up. Love..." Your name here.
当他们被营救  他们可以和你的家庭联系
When they get rescued,they can contact your family.
瓶中信
Message in a bottle.
不错
That's sweet.
-在这里  -好的
-Here you go.  -Okay.
-不要看  -知道了
-Don't look at it.  -Got it.
兄弟
Dude.
-不要看  -好的
-Do not look at it.  -Got it.
-Arzt  你要纸吗?  -已经给过你了
-Arzt! You want paper?  -I gave at the office.
-小心  -好运  兄弟
-Take care.  -Good luck, dude.
-保持干燥  老姐  -我会的
-Keep dry, kiddo.  -I will.
-好运  -你也一样
-Good luck.  -Same to you.
-希望很快会见到你  -你会的
-See you soon.  -Yes, you will.
-小家伙  -什么事
-Hey, guy.  -Yeah?
照顾好你的父亲  好吗?
You look after your dad, okay?
-我会的  -好的
-I will.  -All right.
好运
Good luck.
看见Sawyer了吗?
Hey, have you seen Sawyer?
没有
No.
我们该走了
Let's go!
保重  好吗?
Take care, okay?
这是怎么弄伤的?
Where'd you get the scratches?
一个矮树丛
A bush.
你是说矮树丛
Mean bush.
我们必须往前走了
We'd better keep moving.
我有些问题想问你  Arnzt
Let me ask you something, Arnzt.
Arnzt
不  不是Arnzt Arzt A-R-Z-T. Arzt
Not Arnzt. Arzt. A-R-Z-T.
对不起   你的名字不太好念
Sorry, man,name's hard to pronounce.
是吗?我知道很多九年级生说的很好
I know a bunch of ninth graders who pronounce it just fine.
我就叫你的姓怎么样?
How about I call you by your first name?
-最好别?  -为什么不?
-How about you don't.  -Why not?
我从飞机乘客名单表里知道的
I remember it from the plane's manifest.
我想Leslie是个女人用的名字
Leslie's a bitching name.
叫我Arnzt就可以了
"Arnzt" is fine.
黑暗地带
The Dark Territory.
离黑岩不远了
The Black Rock is not far.
这里是一切开始的地方
This is where it all began,
我的小组在这里被感染
when my team got infected,
Montand失去了手臂
when Montand lost his arm.
我们必须马上离开这
We must move quickly.
你知道吗?
You know what?
我要回去了
I'm going back.
我以为你是来帮忙的
Hey, I thought you wanted to help.
是的  我想帮忙
Yeah, I wanted to help,
但是那是在Montand失去手臂之前
before Montand lost his frigging arm.
那炸药怎么办?
What about the dynamite?
只要小心点就可以了
Just be very careful with it.
不  不  不
No!
这个放在那儿  那个放这儿
This one goes there,that one goes there.
好的  好的
Okay, okay.
头儿
Hey, chief!
削过并且长度也量好了
Cut and measured to length.
一个完美的桅杆
Perfect mast.
谢谢
Thanks.
好了
Well, all right.
我们是把它安装上呢还是继续在这里调侃?
Are we gonna get off this rock or just stand around talking about it?
你们听见了吗?
Did you hear that?
快跑! 快跑! 快跑!
Run! Run! Run!
快跑啊!
Run!
你在干什么?
What are you...?
别动!
Just be still.
在这儿
Here! In here.
进里面来
In here.
兄弟  我们要藏起来
Dude, we gotta book.
等一下
Wait.
它去那边了
It's headed the other way.
我们现在安全了
We're safe now.
那是什么东西?
What was that thing?
只是个安全系统
It's a security system.
安全系统?
Security system?
那是什么意思?
What does that mean?
和其他安全系统一样
Its purpose is that of any security system's
用来保护什么东西
To protect something.
保护什么?
Protect what?
这个岛
The island.
Arnzt在哪里?
Uh, where's Arnzt?
是Arzt  你这个白痴
That's Arzt, you idiot.
兄弟  我还以为你死了呢
Dude, I thought you were dead.
我们赶紧去把炸药弄来好不?
Can we just please go get the dynamite? Please?
你为什么要把这些衣服叠起来?
Why are you folding clothes?
因为我是个疯子
Because I'm anal
这里有你需要的么?
Is there something you want?
我想你应该带上Vincent
I think you should take Vincent.
你是认真的吗?
Are you serious?
它会照顾你
He'll take care of you.
你怎么会认为我需要一只狗来照顾呢?
What makes you think I need a dog to take care of me?
在我妈妈去世后  Vincent一直在照顾我
Vincent took care of me when my mom died.
没有人和我说话
And nobody would talk to me.
他们假装好像什么都没有发生
They pretended like nothing happened.
我有话就告诉Vincent
So I talked to Vincent.
他是一个好的聆听者
He's a good listener.
如果你愿意的话 可以和他说说Boone
You could talk to him about Boone if you want.
好吧
All right.
但是只到你们来营救我们  好吗?
But only until you get us rescued, okay?
不好意思  能帮我照看一下我的包么?
Excuse me. Would you mind watching my bag for a moment?
我马上就回来
I'll be right back.
-当然  没什么  -谢谢
-Sure. Whatever.  -Thank you.
不能买到头等仓的票
Couldn't get us into first class.
为什么不能?
Why not?
也许你不应该对门票代理商大吵大闹
Um, maybe you shouldn't have yelled at the gate agent.
什么  你又站在他那边了?
What, you're on his side now?
总有一天你会感激我为你所做的一切
One day you'll appreciate everything I do for you.
是的  我已经等不急那天了
Yeah, I can't wait for that day.
你可以在门票代理商那里再试一次
Try again with the gate agent.
你能不能放弃?
Would you let it go?
对不起我对你同情的不够
Excuse me for not being pathetic enough
在接下来15个小时坐在什么哭泣的婴儿旁
to want to sit next to a crying baby for the next 15 hours.
上帝
Oh, God,
你想变成一个婊子
you can be a bitch.
你想试试看么?
Oh, you wanna play?
我会把你扔下飞机
I'll get you thrown off this flight.
是吗? 你要怎么做?
How you gonna do that?
我想做什么就做什么  我可以告诉他们...
I can do what I want.I can tell them...
告诉他们什么?
Tell them what?
谁会相信你?
Who's gonna believe you?
你不是有能力...
You're not even capable of...
你不知道我有多大的能力
You have no idea what I am capable of.
-对不起 先生?  -是的  女士
-Excuse me, sir.  -Yes, ma'am.
一个阿拉伯人把他的包留在下面的椅子上
Some Arab guy left his bags in the chairs downstairs
然后就走开了
and walked away.
你能描述下吗?
Can you describe him, please?
阿拉伯人?
Um... Arab.
他向商店走去了
He went towards the shops.
怎么样?
How's that?
我带了些东西给你
I salvaged a few things for you from the Beechcraft.
这是飞机的雷达发射器
This is the plane's radar emitter.
可以把它安装在桅杆上或者船舱的顶部
It needs to be mounted on the mast or the top of the cabin.
我来弄吧
I'll do it.
Michael  节约能量
Michael, to conserve power,
每隔一小时打开一次
turn it on only once every hour or so.
它会告诉你地平线上
It will show you any ships within the horizon line,
大约25英里内的所有船只
approximately 25 miles.
无线电发射器也一样
The same with the radio transmitter.
这是飞机工具箱里照明弹
This was in the plane's toolbox.
只有一发
There's only one flare.
用之前要想清楚了
Choose wisely when you use it.
怎么不走了?
Why are we stopping?
因为我们到了
Because we're here.
这就是黑岩
This is the Black Rock.
怎么这么慢?
我真的是饿坏了
有很多人在排队
没有太多的选择
只能买到这些了
这里
如果你想我为你做那些  杀了我把
You will ever catch me doing anything like that for you, shoot me.
不要那么说  他们的离婚率比我们低20%
Don't knock it. Their divorce rate's 20 times lower than ours.
这是 "艺伎回忆录"出现在真实的生活里
My God, it's Memoirs of a Geisha come to life.
小声点
Hey, volume.
放心  他们又不说英语
Relax. They don't speak English.
这是给你的
S-star...
右舷
Star... Starboard.
Starboard.
那是一些常用的单词 我注上了发音
你应该用的上 就帮你写下来了
对不起
我也是
你不一定要走的
你还不明白吗  Sun?
我在这里是因为我被惩罚
是我让你也受罪
你不应该遭受这些
Jin-
我必须走是因为我要救你
和Jack呆在一起
他会保护你的
谁会保护你呢
我爱你
对不起
没有事的
-走  走  走  走!  -再见了  Vincent!
-Go, go, go, go!  -Bye, Vincent!
再见  Vincent!
Bye, Vincent!
太棒了!
That's it.
呆在那里  Vincent!
Stay, Vincent!
回去  Vincent!
Go back, Vincent!
Vincent!
回去!
go back!
回去啊!
Go back!
我说什么来着  哈?
What'd I tell ya, huh?
我们成功了!
We did it!
兄弟!
You! Whoo!
==============| YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报 ====